http://www.outmotoring.com/privacy-policy.html

Motoring Rewards
Earn cash as you shop!
Which MINI model?
Buy the right parts.
MINI Club Support
Free stuff for your Club!
Free Shipping
Click for details
100% Happiness
Easy returns + exchanges
A Hitch for your MINI?
Yes,we've got hitches!
865-223-6335TEXT or CALL
Cart (0)
Search In...
Blog
Select your Model:
SelectModel:
Select Category...
about us
What MINI Cooper Model Do I Have?
Newsletter Signup
Sign up here for MINI Newsletters. Get Monthly discount codes!
MINI Cooper Blog
View most popular Blog articles...
View all Blog entries...
Choose a Category from our blog...
MINI Cooper Acccessories + MINI Cooper Parts
::
privacy policy
privacy policy
Out Motoring, Inc. (hereinafter Out Motoring) values the privacy of our visitors/customers and takes every known precaution to safe guard the information we collect from unauthorized use.  The following is a detailed explanation of the privacy policy for Out Motoring.
WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT?
Out Motoring believes it is important for you to know what types of information we collect when you use our site.  We employ various methods for collecting information.  To begin with, we use cookies that are needed to compile aggregate non-personally identifiable information about the visitors to our web site. Personally identifiable information consists of information that is unique to you, such as credit card numbers, home address, email address and the like.  This is the type of information that most people consider private and deem the most important to protect from unauthorized access.  Non-personally identifiable information most often consists of things such as your search preferences, the types of products you have bought, how many times you have visited a particular web site, etc.  This type of information is usually associated with a particular computer or IP address but not with a particular person. Cookies are pieces of information generated by a Web server and stored in the user's computer, ready for future access.  Each time you access our web site; our server finds the relevant cookie on your computer.  The information contained within that cookie is then used to customize your experience with our site.  The following is a list of the information we collect: (names, address, phone numbers, email address, credit card number, car model and year)
WHY DO WE COLLECT THIS INFORMATION?
We use this information in order to serve the needs of our customers.  We need to know who you are in order to verify the credit card information you have sent us.  We collect several pieces of personal information from you in order to complete this verification process.  The non-personal information that we collect from you is used in order to offer you better service and to make your experience with our site more enjoyable.  Any credit card information that is used to complete a transaction is never seen by our staff nor is it is stored on our computers. We use one of the leading data protection and credit card gateways, Authorize.net, to handle all encrypted data and to confirm all payment info.
HOW IS YOUR INFORMATION PROTECTED?
We use the latest in encryption technology, including 128 bit SSL encryption to ensure that any sensitive information that is sent by you to us via the Internet is protected from unauthorized interception.  We employ the latest in firewall protection to prevent unauthorized access into our information storage areas.  We maintain a rigorous hiring process to screen out potential employees with criminal backgrounds.  Passwords are required in order for you to gain access to your account, however we do NOT store credit card information on our customers account database.
WHO HAS ACCESS TO MY INFORMATION?
Only those employees that are responsible for handling your account have access to your information.  Additionally, employees in our technical department may have access to your information in order to conduct routine checks on the integrity of our system and in order to perform necessary maintenance work.  In order to process your credit card we have to consult with an out side credit card processing company called Authorize.net.  These processing companies are regulated by the banking industry and must meet certain security requirements in order to be in business.  The processing companies will have access to your credit card information, billing address, name, and possibly your telephone number.  The processing company will communicate with the issuing bank of your credit card in order to get final approval to charge your credit card for the product or services we are providing for you.  Should you choose to receive additional information regarding one of our services or products, we may pass your email address to one of our partners who offers similar products or services that you might be interested in.  Additionally, judicial requests by a duly authorized court will require us to divulge certain information regarding your account should that situation arise.  Finally, should our company ever be bought or sold, your account information would then become the property of the new owner/entity.
CAN I CORRECT OR REMOVE INFORMATION FROM YOUR SITE?
You always have the option to view your account to make sure the information we have collected from you is indeed correct.  You also have the option of removing any information from your account that you wish to keep private.  However, please note that removing certain information such as your email address, contact information, and the like may greatly hinder our ability to effectively provide the service or products you have requested.  We recommend, that you contact us first to discuss which information you may remove without interrupting the quality of service we intend to provide for you.
CAN I OPT OUT OF HAVING CERTAIN INFORMATION COLLECTED?
You have the option of disabling your computers ability to accept or transmit cookies.  This will prevent us from gathering certain non-personally identifiable information from you.  You also have the option of removing yourself from any email distribution list that you may have signed up for.
NOTICE OF CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY
We reserve the right to change this privacy policy at any time.  However, if any changes do occur, we will publish the changes to our web site and post a notice on the home page that a new privacy policy has been implemented.  We will also take reasonable steps to contact you personally to let you know of the new changes.  Should the company be bought or sold to someone else, we will take reasonable steps to notify you personally.  You will then be given the option to keep your account open or to terminate.
WHAT ABOUT EMAIL LISTS AND MY INFO?
We will likely send promotional emails noting special offers or new products we think you'll enjoy knowing about. If you would not like to receive any information from us please use our automated email newsletter system which has a integrated unsubscribe feature in every newsletter email we send. We may also automatically add you to the mailing list if you have ordered from us. If you receive emails from us and would like to have your email removed from the list please follow the automated newsletter removal process described in the email. Please note that WE DO NOT SELL ANY INFORMATION GATHERED FROM OUR CLIENTS.
Product photos do not always reflect the exact product for sale.
We do not guarantee that all items on our website are available to ship at the time you place your order. We will do our best to communicate with you any updates and delays in shipping.
All prices are subject to change without notice. Please understand if we, at some time, need to update our pricing.
All products are sold with manufacturer's warranty, where applicable. No other warranty is expressed or implied. Some products sold are for race use only and are not to be used on a public streets. Please check your local laws regarding the installation of these products.
Out Motoring will not be held liable for any labor, incidental or consequential damages of any kind.
Motoring Rewards
Earn cash as you shop!
Which MINI model?
Buy the right parts.
MINI Club Support
Free stuff for your Club!
Free Shipping
Click for details
100% Happiness
Easy returns + exchanges
A Hitch for your MINI?
Yes,we've got hitches!
OutMotoring!
Forgot password?
Sign up for MINI Newsletters. Get Monthly discount codes!
Call for help
865-223-6335
m-th: 9-5 EST
fri:
9-1 EST
